var hawaiian = [
	{
		front: "the boy",
		back: "ke keikikane"
	}, {
		front: "the girl",
		back: "ke kaikamahine"
	}, {
		front: "the man",
		back: "ke kane"
	},{
		front: "the woman",
		back: "ka wahine"
	}, {
		front: "the family",
		back: "ka ohana"
	}, {
		front: "the house",
		back: "ka hale"
	}, {
		front: "the food",
		back: "ka mea'ai"
	}, {
		front: "hello",
		back: "aloha"
	}, {
		front: "good morning",
		back: "aloha kakahiaka"
	}, {
		front: "good evening",
		back: "aloha ahiahi"
	}, {
		front: "goodbye",
		back: "aloha"
	}, {
		front: "please",
		back: "me ka 'olu'olu"
	}, {
		front: "thank you",
		back: "mahalo"
	}
];

module.exports = hawaiian;